Change to the round tool in the salad menu
Press the Shift key and click and drag the mouse button in the 2D window to manually create a positive circle
To see the positive and negative sides of the surface,
switch to the physical surface, which is the single layer display
After selecting the version, select the outer layer of the column in the menu in the menu bar
Create a version that is identical and interactive with it
At the same time, select these two versions
Press the Shift key and drag the mouse button in the 2D window to create a new version
Press the Shift key and drag and drag the mouse button in the 2D window to create a new version
can be diluted to 45 degrees or 90 degrees to arrange the board
Separate the two boards to make it easier for everyone to see the positive and negative sides
When we apply the pressure of the positive number to a board
The board will receive a horizontal force from the back to the positive side
When applying the pressure of the negative number to a board
The board will receive a horizontal force from the front to the back
After opening the simulation, we will see that this round-shaped pillow is complete
If now we change the bottom of this board to the positive number of pressure
Both boards have the force from the back to the positive side
The force imbalance will be lost
So when two boards face each other on the back and face each other on the front
The pressure values must be the same
And the pressure of the board facing the front must be the positive number
The pressure of the board facing the back must be the negative number to balance
If both sides face each other on the front
Then the value of one positive and one negative will also fly away
When both boards face each other on the front
If the pressure needs to be balanced, it needs to be set to the positive number.
So let's see what happens when two boards face each other on the front and face each other on the back
The pressure values of both boards are the same
The more the pressure values are the more the air supply effect is more obvious
The pressure values of both boards face each other on the front and face each other on the back
The physical property will also affect the air supply effect
The stronger the elite board is and the lower the resistance to the angle line
The easier it is to stretch the fabric
It will swell up more after the pressure
second simulation you will see that it has swelled up into a ball
Now let's take a look at the actual use of pressure.
Now this sleeve plate is a separate plate and is facing the outside.
If we need to make the sleeve pop up, we can apply positive pressure for it.
After changing the pressure value, we can see that the sleeve is popping up.
The elastic strength of this sleeve material is too high for the foot line tension, and it is not easy to stretch, so we need to reduce it a little bit to make the pressure more obvious.
Now let's take a look at the actual use of pressure.
After changing the pressure value, we can see that the sleeve is popping up.
In addition, if you want to sew a wide plate onto a narrow plate, remember to apply the elastic strength to the shorter side.
For example, we open the elastic strength, and the value is set to 100.
Let's take a look at the actual use of pressure.
We can see that the pressure is still there, and the upper part of the sleeve is not pulled open by the pressure.
If we don't apply the elastic strength, we can see that the sewing line will pull the two sides to the middle, so the short side will be stretched.
However, after applying the elastic strength of 100, the side will not be stretched anymore, and the pressure will be more obvious.
We can also reduce the elastic strength to make the pressure more obvious.
Now let's take a look at the other uses of positive pressure.
Now there is a skirt, and the plates are all facing outwards.
After applying the positive pressure, the skirt will gradually expand due to the pressure.
After the skirt is opened, it will become smaller, and the skirt will float in the air.
If we change the pressure value to 2, it will become smaller.
Because it means that if we change the pressure value to 2, the girl won't be very happy.
If we change the pressure value to 2, the skirt will be a bit loose.
The result of the chaotic DOWN and down cope is from both sides.
When we cooling the skirt, we can see that there are Pulls that we need to cool.
Because they are not transmitted correctly, they are relatively isolated.
but it still retains a certain amount of looseness.
Next, let's take a look at how to apply the negative pressure.
Now that the edge of the contract is finished,
it is not very close to the model.
By modifying the pressure to the negative value,
you can apply pressure from the front of the fabric to the back,
and the edge of the contract is close to the model.
Next, let's take a look at how to use the pressure to make a inflatable t-shirt.
First, use the internal line tool to draw an internal line and copy and paste it.
After pressing Ctrl V,
press the right key to open the paste menu and enter the number of pasting.
Then you can choose to align the internal line to the outer line of the panel,
so that the air line of our t-shirt is finished.
Next, we can cut a layer to make the inflatable effect.
After cutting a layer,
the inner line on the panel
will automatically form an inflatable line.
Select a panel.
If you see the panel on the inside,
then their pressure needs to be set to negative.
The panel on the outside is set to positive pressure,
and the vertical value needs to be the same as the inside.
After opening the simulation,
you can see the clothing inflator
and the internal line position is inflated.
If you don't think the effect is obvious,
you can increase the vertical value
and the horizontal value to 10.
Reducing the tension of the diagonal line
can make the clothing look more fluffy and soft.
Increasing the tension of the diagonal line
can make the impact part look more tight.
Change the elasticity of the clothing to 98
to get the inflatable effect of the air line.
Whether it is the inner layer or the outer layer,
as long as the elasticity is applied, the inflatable effect will increase.
If the inflatable effect is not obvious,
you can increase the strength of the gold-plated gauze.
It will be easier to stretch the panel,
and it will be more likely to have a wrinkle.
At the same time,
reduce the particle diameter
to get a more detailed wrinkle effect.
See you in the next video.
Bye bye.